(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T09:35:19.105476",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
もうこんな時間！
Eh? This time already?!
遅刻だあああ！
Nooo, I'm late!
墓から這い上がる姿はこんなのか？
So this is how you look when you're fresh out of the grave?
さて、お化粧の時間です
Alright, time for a makeover!
靴チェック、服チェック、リボンチェック。よし、オールグリーン！
Shoes check, uniform check, ribbons check. Nice, everything's ready.
やりー！ついにやお披露目か！
Finally, our Bestie will do a showcase!
そちらはどう？
How's the situation there?
バックダンサーの準備オーケー
Back dancers are on standby.
ステージもバッチリ
The stage is also clear.
素晴らしい、うまくいくといいね
I'm sure it'll be a smooth show.
んー、これでお利のお菓子は足りるのかな？
Hmm, are these snacks enough for Ollie?
オリー先輩ってたくさん食べるんだっけ？
Doesn't Ollie-senpai usually eat a lot?
クリピック忘れないこと！クリピカチャ！
Oh, add glassy chips! I want glassy chips!
いやいや、ちょっと待って！ステージ上でむせちゃったらどうするの？
That's not a good idea. You don't want to make her cough on stage.
それじゃあ水をいっぱ増やしちゃうか？
Shall we bring more drinks instead?
そうだ！それな！
Ah, that's good!
やっとここまで来たか
I've come this far.
みんな…みんながオリーを応援してて
Everyone... Everyone's been supporting me.
よし！いけるぞ！オリー！がんばれ！オリー！
Come on! I can do this! Do your best, Ollie!
オリー！レッツゴー！
Ollie! Let's freaking go!
ほらほらほら！いけぜ！がんばれ！今日は君の出番だ。グッドラック！
Go, go, let's go! Good luck, Ollie! It's your time to shine. Good luck, Ollie!
あんたならできるよ。がんばれ、オリー！いける！いける！いける！
I know you can do it, Ollie. Go for it, Ollie! Break a leg, Ollie! It's in the bag! You got this! You got this! You got this!
みんな、ありがとう
Thank you, everyone.
よし！視聴者のみんなを感動させようか！
Okay. Let's make everyone weep with joy!
lala lai , lalala i , when our heartbeats collide
lala lai, lalala i, when our heartbeats collide
ho am i in a place we've never been before
oh, in a place we've never been before
i 'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it
I'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it
lala lai , lalala i , is it you i will find ?
lala lai, lalala i, is it you I will find?
though i feel left behind sometimes when you close the door
Though I feel left behind when you close the door,
i wanna know who you are , i wanna know it all
I wanna know who you are, I wanna know it all
the moment that life hits you , you can't avoid the issue
The moment that life hits you, you can't avoid the issue,
you 're disconnected from the world you thought you were part of
you're disconnected from the world you thought you were part of.
but if you close your eyes and let go of that mirage you haven't met ,
But if you close your eyes and let go of that mirage you haven't met,
nobody else decides the words you see in your heart
so line up , the party 's over here , come one , come all , come on and jump into the fire
So line up, the party's over here, come one, come all, come on and jump into the fire!
step up , we are whatever we wanna be , we 're free to slide all of us are
Step up, we are whatever we wanna be, we're free to slide all of us are.
when you pass through the veil of fantasy , there 's a world with a rhythm for you and me
When you pass through the veil of fantasy, there's a world with a rhythm for you and me.
lala lai , lalala i , how can i find a love lost in time ?
lala lai, lalala i, how can I find a love lost in time?
there 's an answer in the stars for me all the way across the galaxy , go on forever
There's an answer in the stars for me all the way across the galaxy, go on forever.
lala lai , lalala i , i will follow the signs 'cause i know when i reach the end it 's you i 'll see
lala lai, lalala i, I will follow the signs 'cause I know when I reach the end it's you I'll see.
though we can't waste our time here , it 's now or never
Though we can't waste our time here, it's now or never!
the relentless force of nature , the visage of our future
The relentless force of nature, the visage of our future,
sometimes i know it feels like fate is never on our side
but as i stand inside the vortex , i wanna have you here beside me
But as I stand inside the vortex, I wanna have you here beside me,
you 're all i need to leap into a perfect sky !
you're all I need to leap into a perfect sky!
stand up , the party 's over here , come one , come all , let 's follow the north star
Stand up, the party's over here, come one, come all, let's follow the north star!
step in you are whatever you wanna be , you are free just like all of us are
Step in, you are whatever you wanna be, you are free just like all of us are.
dance away a world you never loved from the start , it 's our ride to the future , are you ready to depart ?
Dance away a world you never loved from the start, it's our ride to the future, are you ready to depart?
lala lai , lalala i , when our heartbeats collide
lala lai, lalala i, when our heartbeats collide,
i won't mind , in a place we've never been before , i 'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it
I won't mind, in a place we've never been before, I'm reaching out for the moon and stars beyond it.
lala lai , lalala i , is it you i will find ?
lala lai, lalala i, is it you I will find?
though i feel left behind sometimes when you close the door
Though I feel left behind when you close the door,
i wanna know who you are , i wanna know it all
I wanna know who you are, I wanna know it all.
maybe it 's a dream , i don't wanna wake , even if a light goes up , i don't wanna know reality
Maybe it's a dream, I don't wanna wake, even if a light goes up, I don't wanna know reality.
we didn't waste our time here , it 's now or never
We didn't waste our time here, it's now or never!
(huffing / breathing)
(Sighs)
Se-se-seru banget! Super kawaii zombie idol!
It-it was so much fun! Super kawaii zombie idol!
K-k-k-kureiji!
Ollie desu wa! Welcome to my 3D show, guys!
Semua datang di showcase Ollie! Oh ya, udah melar belum?
Everyone came to Ollie's showcase! Oh yeah, have you stretched yet?
Ya, kan sekarang udah 3D. Ollie sekarang udah bisa joget.
Yeah, since it's 3D now, Ollie can dance now.
Wah, ada banyak banget orang nonton.
Wow, there are so many people watching.
Jangan lupa untuk pakai hashtag di sebelah sini ya! Penonton yang nonton kan banyak kan, jadi jangan lupa pakai hashtag di sebelah sini ya!
Don't forget to use the hashtag right here, okay? There are a lot of viewers watching, so don't forget to use the hashtag right here!
Nah, dengan begitu, bagaimana?
Well, with that being said, how is it?
Ollie dah 3D! I can move a lot now!
Ollie's already 3D! I can move a lot now!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Kurenai! Tuh kan, udah disuruh 3D. Kawaii, kan?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Kurenai! See, I told you it's 3D. Cute, right?
Dan dengan new acquired form, aku bisa dance sambil sing now. Aku nggak cuma doang karaoke.
And with this newly acquired form, I can dance while singing now. I don't just do boring karaoke.
I sang 'U' for a millennium created and bow. Udah kangen belum?
I sang 'U' for a millennium created and bow. Did you miss it?
Ya kan, sekarang udah 3D, Ollie sekarang udah bisa joget. Capek.
Yeah right, now that it's 3D, Ollie can dance now. So tired.
Ollie tadi sempat nyanyi U loh, gimana tadi? Keren nggak?
Ollie just sang 'U', how was it? Was it cool?
Itu saksi mau. Muri, gerak, oh, gerak yo?
Those witnesses want to. Muri, moved, oh, moved right?
Jaga, back-up dancers-nya juga, dancer-nya with me, but uh, kita kan ren off. Pas kita finish dancers-nya juga capek, cuma mereka langsung kabur, tidak selesai.
Wait, the back-up dancers too, dancing with me, but uh, we ran off. After we finished, the dancers were tired too, but they just ran off, not finished.
So, back dancers-dancer-nya juga ada ya. Minat-nya kaget yuk, semangat, wah!
So, the back dancers were there too. Everyone was surprised, let's go, spirit, wow!
And look, I'm not just dancing anywhere. I'm dancing in what I called Ollie Streaming!
Dunia Mimpi Ollie!
そうだよ ええとこれはね おりの建てた場所はね おりの夢の世界
That's right, um... this place that I built is, you see, my dream world.
It's Dreamland because it's full of the things that I love.
Dunia Mimpi Ollie
karena aduh capek banget
because... phew, I'm so tired!
Di sini ada banyak hal-hal yang ori sukai gitu.
Here, there are lots of things that Ollie likes.
ここにはねえとおりの好きなものがいっぱいあるよ ちょっと見に行こうかな
Here, um, there are so many things I love. Shall we go take a look?
最初は後ろ From the back! Dan itu ada...
First, behind us! From the back. And there is...
Air mancur strawberry! It's a strawberry milk fountain because I always love strawberry milk, pink milk!
A strawberry milk fountain! It's a strawberry milk fountain because I always love strawberry milk, pink milk!
そうだよえetoいちご牛乳がめったくた好きなのでダファウンテンがありますええとウインドウ開けて！
So, um, because I love strawberry milk so much, there's a fountain! And... open the window!
ほらすごいっしょ そうえとおりはねゆえんちが好きなので
Woo! Look, amazing right? So, um, I like amusement parks,
後ろも遊園地があるよ 見るかなゴンドラ みんな気付いた？ Ada kaya gondola gitu. There's an amusement park ride behind where I'm dancing! Pretty cool!
so there's an amusement park behind us too! Can you see the gondola? Did you guys notice? There's like... a gondola. There's an amusement park ride behind where I'm dancing! Pretty cool!
And then if we go over here, continue attara...
And then if we go over here, if we continue...
ほら いっぱい花があるよ My beautiful flowers ya!
Look, there are so many flowers! My beautiful flowers, yeah!
And I'm sure you guys have noticed, butada bapak yago... Sungguh bapak yago! Terima kasih bapak, berkat bapak saya bisa debut jadi 3D.
And I'm sure you guys have noticed, but there's Papa Yagoo... Truly Papa Yagoo! Thank you, Papa. Thanks to you, I was able to debut in 3D!
Itches pieces! And you guys can't really see it, but... blub, blub, uh... yago-san, there's like a Shogi piece. Oh, I guess that's for another day.
It's chess pieces! And you guys can't really see it, but... yeah, Yagoo-san, there's like a Shogi piece. Well, I guess that's for another day.
And wait, actually, uh I'm not the only one who can move around, we can do an other language sekurakada. ええとそしてね、おりだけではなく、もう１人が３Dができたよ！
And wait, actually, I'm not the only one who can move around. We can do another language! Sekurakada. And also, not just Ollie, but someone else got their 3D too!
ええと…えー！オーリー！お、 terima kasih kawan-teman! Terima kasih creator!
Um... ehh! Ollie! Oh, thank you friends! Thank you creator!
kasi sudah datang, wah! Keren-keren-keren, banyak odinya ya. And thank you. Just dancing all over the place.
Thanks for coming. So cool, so many Ollies, yeah? And thank you. Just dancing all over the place.
はっ、そうだったら、オリーはなんか１人ウdinで、で、お勧めオリー。 ada gaya... Udin!
Hah, in that case, Ollie feels like she needs one Udin to keep Ollie company. Pose, Udin!
Udin, Udin! Oh, oh dia, Hai Udin! Say hi to the camera!
Udin, Udin. Oh, there he is. Hi, Udin! Say hi to the camera!
Hoi! Oh, good job! Good job. Mutar-mutar-mutar-mutar. Siap belum? Ah... Terusilur, but. Um, tork. Ah, meccha ii. Keren kan?
Hoi! Oh, good job. Good job. Spin, spin, spin, spin. Narrow? Ah, so cute, but wait, twerk. Ah, so good. So cool, right?
Udin, high-five, high-five, high-five. Pendek sekali, eh. Pendek banget, jadi sulit kan? Makanya yo. Ya, kalau gitu, udah lu, sana pergi. His!
Udin, high-five, high-five, high-five. So short. Eh, super short. Makes it difficult, huh? That's why. Yeah, in that case, you guys, go away over there. Hiss!
Ya, ja, eto tanoshikatta ne! Ah, berikutnya Ollie masih ada beberapa hal yang pengen Ollie tunjukin kepada kalian. Jadi jangan kalian ke mana-mana. I still have so many things I want to show you guys, so don't go anywhere. Yos, sore ja tsugi no kyoku ni ikou kana? Let's go!
Yeah, that was fun! Next, Ollie still has a few more things she wants to show you guys, so don't go anywhere. I still have so many things I want to show you guys, so don't go anywhere. Alright, shall we move on to the next song? Let's go!
ワッハウィーアーゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombies!
知りたい知りたい 聞き飽むるまで ルールに囚われていたいのだ
I want to know, I want to know, until I'm sick of hearing it, I want to be bound by the rules
会いたい会いたい 欠けれないじゃん 釣られていたい 動けないのなんでなんで
I want to see you, I want to see you, I can't miss it, I want to be reeled in, why can't I move? Why, why?
寂しさだけのトワイライト
A twilight of pure loneliness
満ちてはねって満ちてはねって なんだだって恋を続けるんで
Filling and ebbing, filling and ebbing, no matter what, I'll keep on loving
気づこそして 口を吸って なんだだって恋がしたい
Realizing, then kissing, no matter what, I want to fall in love
だって知っちゃってるの アイラビュー アイラビュー 抱きしめてもいいでしょ
Because I already know it, I love you, I love you, it's okay to hold me, right?
さりげなくてもいいでしょ アイラビュー アイラビュー 二人だけのシークレット
Playing around with no real meaning, I love you, I love you, a secret just for the two of us
ワッハウィーアーゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombies!
時々がもどかしくて
Sometimes it's so frustrating
ワッハウィーアーゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombies!
ギュッとしてまっすぐ今まま なんちゃって冗談じゃないね
Hugging me straight on right now, just kidding, I'm totally serious
ワッハウィーアーゾンビ
Wah-ha, we are zombies!
懲り懲りズム 欠き気味 欠き気味よ 噛み付いて プリーズ プリーズ 止められないよ
Fed up with the rhythm, lacking, lacking, bite me, please, please, I can't stop it
シシトウ かぎどし じゃなくぽつり 芽生えわ で も
Shishito, hooking up, not just a casual drop, sprouts appear, but even so
懲り懲りズム 欠き気味 欠き気味よ 噛み付いて プリーズ プリーズ 止められないよ
Fed up with the rhythm, lacking, lacking, bite me, please, please, I can't stop it
シシトウ かぎどし じゃなくぽつり 芽生えわ で も
Shishito, hooking up, not just a casual drop, sprouts appear, but even so
それじゃあおやすみなさいって
So then, saying goodnight
私なっちゃってっ てるの
I'm turning into...
アイラヴユー アイラヴユー 腐りかけもいいね
I love you, I love you, decomposing is fine too
きみもなっちゃえば？
Why don't you turn too?
アイラヴユー アイラヴユー ふたりだけのシークレット
I love you, I love you, our little secret
ふたりなっちゃって えば アイラヴユー アイラヴユー
If we both turn, I love you, I love you
死なないからいいじゃん
It's fine since we won't die
愛し合っちゃえば アイラヴユー アイラヴユー
If we love each other, I love you, I love you
きみ以外はないね
There's no one else but you
ないねないね
No one else, no one else
わっはー We’re ゾンビ ゾンビ
Wa-ha! We're zombie zombies
きらきらもっと光るんだ
Shining even brighter
きみ撫でられても痒くないよ
Now, even if you stroke me, it doesn't tickle
もう噛み付いてても美味しくないよ
Even if you bite me, it's not delicious anymore
嫉妬吐き出しちゃうジャックポット
Spitting out jealousy like a jackpot
縫い目はデマ それ以上仰からないで
The stitches are fake, so don't pry any further
引きずって歩いてるのなんでなんで
Why can't I stop dragging this along?
寂しさだけのこっちゃってんだ
All that's left behind is just loneliness
涙止まんない
I can't stop crying...
Personal... Sami... もう疲れちゃった...
Personal... Sami... I'm all worn out...
あー... もう... やばいですね！ I practiced a lot!
Ah... Man, that's rough! I practiced a lot!
You guys would never know! ほら、踊れ...
You guys would never know! Come on, dance...
倒れた... 大丈夫です、I'm okay!
I fell down... I'm okay!
危なかったの... 次次！自分のうちに行こうか
That was close... Next, next! Let's go to my house!
車もない出掛りゃ... 別に... いやなんでもない... We're going to my house!
No car to take us there... Never mind... We're going to my house!
I'm getting ramen! Let's go!
お腹減った... I'm so hungry!
I'm so hungry!
まーがん、まーがん、まーがん、ゾンベー！We're finally here at the ramen shop!
Ramen, ramen, ramen, zombie! We finally made it to the ramen shop!
No, it's not the ramen shop, it's my house!
ラーメン屋じゃないよ、これはウチのウチだよ！
This isn't a ramen shop, this is Ollie's house!
ええっとね、ここはテレビがあるはず...
And um, there used to be a TV over here...
And over here used to be a sofa...
But I don't see it anymore.
It's a little bit sad and frustrating!
だけど、まあいっか、もう出掛けたからね！だからもう気にならないでいいか！
But oh well, we're already out, so let's not worry about it!
お腹がもうペコペコだから...
My tummy is already rumbling, so...
まいっか！食べようかラーメン！Let's just go and make some ramen! Let's go!
Let's just go and make some ramen! Let's go!
The kitchen should be this way...
どこにあるんだろね？Self service, here I go!
Where is it? Self-service, here I go!
着いた！This is the kitchen!
Found it! This is the kitchen!
ここは台所で、ここは調理器具を Ollie cari dulu. Ah, mana ya? Cari-cari.
This is where Ollie looks around first. Let me search.
Gasak-gosok, gasak-gosok. Ketemu! Ehehehe.
Scrub-a-dub, scrub-a-dub... Found it! Hehehe!
Ini ya, teman-teman, Ollie udah belajar... yukiri, ya kan?
This, my friends, Ollie has already learned. Yukiri, right?
Soshite ugoku! Dakara yukiri...
And then it moves! That's why yukiri...
Ini namanya yukiri, cara gerakannya. Udah, kita masak aja.
This is called yukiri, that's how it moves. Let's just cook!
I'm so hungry! Ugh, susah. Perlahan-lahan, just slowly, there we go!
I'm so hungry! Ugh, difficult. Slowly, just slowly, there we go!
And with that, let me just put this down, gasak-gosok. And our ramen is done!
And with that, let me just put this down, scrub-a-dub, and our ramen is done!
Kanse! Kanse!
Done, done!
Susu hijau nggak? Ya, tapi yudah lah, kita makan aja kali ya! Let's go and have a lunch!
Smells good, doesn't it? Let's just eat! Let's go and have some lunch!
Ya, makan-makan! Emang kalau Ollie yang masak itu, mantap kan?
Yeah, let's eat! If Ollie cooks it, it's amazing, right?
Self service keren juga ya!
Self-service is pretty cool too!
Nah, kita makan sambil duduk kayak lady gitu kan ya?
Now, let's eat while sitting down like a lady, shall we?
Itadakimasu!
Manda pseteba banget!
So appetizing!
Hmm! Enak! Enak! Enak! It's so delicious!
Mmm! Delicious! It's so delicious!
Terus habis itu... kita habisin kuahnya. Gok-gok-gok...
And after that, we finish the broth. Gulp gulp gulp...
Gochisousama deshita! Thank you so much!
Oh gosh, I have myself to thank. Thank you, Ollie! That was really good!
And then, what else should we eat? Some dessert, maybe? Konata dessert ada tak tabeokana?
And then, what else should we eat? Some dessert, maybe? Let's have some dessert!
え？あれ？誰がお客さま？Is that a customer I see?
Huh? Who's that customer? Is that a customer I see?
Hello, apa kabar, anda punya long gun?
Hello, how are you, do you have a long gun?
Whoa! Itu pistol! That's a gun, ju desune! Yabai!
Whoa! That's a pistol! That's a handgun, ju desune! Yabai!
Ini ondo kengang kinian! Ollie masih belum siap mentalnya, gogorojemeo...
This is way too intense! Ollie's mental state isn't ready yet!
Well, you know what? That's okay,
because I myself have my own gun!
Ollie juga punya pistol sendiri, lihat nih!
Ollie also has her own gun, look at this!
Gasak-gasak!
Take that!
Lebih besar kan? Motor size-nya.
It's bigger, right? Motor-sized.
It's even bigger than yours, right?
Well then, take this! Kena! Rasakan ini!
Well then, take this! Hit! Feel this!
Angkat tangan! Saya angkat tangan. Terima kasih.
Hands up! I give up. Thank you.
Jangan, jangan... jangan pukul saya. Don't hurt me, please don't hurt me!
Don't, don't... don't hurt me. Don't hurt me, please don't hurt me!
Oh, okay. What? You want me to raise my hand higher?
Bagaimanakah, ya? Kenapa tinggikan tangannya?
How should I do this? Why raise my hand?
Oh, itu mau Anda, ya? Gini, gini, gini.
Oh, is that what you want? Like this, like this.
Gini, gini, gini.
Like this, like this, like this.
Kayaknya enggak ada, ya? Mau sepi, kah?
Seems like there's none, huh? Is it deserted?
Diputar-putar, kelilingi... kaget.
Spinning around, going around... startling.
Well, you know what? That's fine.
Well then, after this, I'm going to show you guys... Whoa!
Dipikir-pikir lagi, ya. Seharusnya itu tadi senjata Ollie pakai untuk nembak.
Come to think of it, I should have just used my gun to shoot.
Well, if you think about it, I should have just used my gun. Yeah, FPS-nya kalau mau keraba, ya, gawat-lah!
Well, if you think about it, I should have just used my gun. Yeah, FPS skills would be terrible otherwise!
逃げるなら今だけよ
If you're going to run, now's the only time,
勝利を願いちゃって！
Wishing for victory!
(あい) you are noob
(Ah) you are noob.
もう知ってんのさ
I already know it.
入念な漁りに15 minutes xd
Thorough looting with 15 minutes xd.
身を潜めて走る先に ほら誰か
Hiding and running ahead, look, someone is there.
銃声！scanning！
Gunshots! Scanning!
(あっ) ロビーでスタンバイには
(Ah) Standing by in the lobby,
(んー) もう正直飽き飽きなのよ
(Hmm) I'm honestly sick and tired of it.
ランクマは残酷 私には血の味ね
Ranked is cruel, to me it tastes like blood.
フラグメント？実に対抗的
Fragment? Truly competitive.
medikitの山とp2020
A mountain of medikits and a P2020.
(oh) good luck？
(Oh) good luck?
祈る幸運なんかなりより 確かな実力？
Rather than praying for luck, solid skill?
day by day 初動死 粗粗
Day by day, dying off-drop, crude.
やりたいこと全部pingを刺した
Pinging everything I want to do.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's fine if you laughed at me,
前には出られないkraberが怖過ぎて
Scared of the Kraber so I can't step forward.
(victory to the world's edge)
(Victory to World's Edge)
手に入れたバッジと感動は
The badge and emotions I obtained
きっとかけがえがないはずよ
Must be truly irreplaceable.
見せてみてよこの狂地へ
Show me, to this land of madness,
いらっしゃって！
Welcome!
忘れたリロード
Forgotten reload,
ついてこないランク
Rank that doesn't keep up,
買い並べた豪華なスキン
Luxuriously lined-up skins.
広大すぎる大地の上
Upon the vast, sprawling land,
ここはどこだ？over
Where is this? Over.
拾い上げた1 killが
The 1 kill I picked up
そう私を強くしていくわ
Is making me stronger.
positioning！
Positioning!
高所から覗かれるのは癪
Annoyed at being peered at from above,
(oh) shhh！軽快に1.2.3.
(Oh) shhh! Lightly 1, 2, 3.
●ぬのは嫌でtrip→trip
I hate dying, trip -> trip.
気がつけばround 3でアレレ…隠れていただけ？
Before I knew it, round 3, huh? Just hiding?
night and dayで fighting 辛辛
Fighting day and night, struggling hard,
ラグなんかじゃないのは全部分かってる
Knowing fully well it's not lag at all.
泣いたって辞めないさこれが私の
I won't quit even if I cry, this is my
kill pointになるとも知らずにね
Unknowing that it will become a kill point.
(victory to the world's edge)
(Victory to World's Edge)
共に掴み叩きたいんだ
Together we want to grasp and strike
熱きド頭ん中を
Our passionate minds.
心地いいのこの狂地に染まっちゃって！
Soaking into this pleasant madness!
b.p.m 走ったって
Running at a high B.P.M.,
a.i.m はブレないで
Without shaking your A.I.M.
day by day 潜ってまだまだ
Diving day by day, still and all,
モニター越しにアイコンタクトとって
Making eye contact through the monitor.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's fine if you laughed at me,
ただみんなにいつかチャンピオンと呼ばすだけ
Just making everyone call me champion someday.
(victory to the world's edge)
(Victory to World's Edge)
絶対追い抜くよ
I'll definitely surpass you,
あの光るダイブ軌道を
That glowing dive trail.
忘れられないほどの勝利を願いちゃって
Hoping for victory so unforgettable,
狂地を行こうgg！
Let's go to the land of madness, gg!
b.p.m 走ったって
Running at a high B.P.M.,
a.i.m はブレないで
Without shaking your A.I.M.
day by day 潜ってまだまだ
Diving day by day, still and all,
モニター越しにアイコンタクトとって
Making eye contact through the monitor.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
It's fine if you laughed at me,
ただみんなにいつかチャンピオンと呼ばすだけ
Just making everyone call me champion someday.
(victory to the world's edge)
(Victory to World's Edge)
絶対追い抜くよ
I'll definitely surpass you,
あの光るダイブ軌道を
That glowing dive trail.
忘れられないほどの勝利を願いちゃって
Hoping for victory so unforgettable,
狂地を行こうgg！
Let's go to the land of madness, gg!
Duh...
Ugh...
Ni mana?
Where is this?
Ah...
Kayak-nya Ollie barusan mimpi enak deh.
Looks like Ollie just had a nice dream.
Kayak habis jadi pro gamer gitu.
Like I just became a pro gamer.
Hah, ini tangan kaki pada oh di situ, bisa copot gitu.
Huh, these hands and feet are... oh, over there, they can detach like that.
Eh, kaki! Ker ker ker ker ker ker... Good kaki, good kaki, good kaki!
Hey, leg! Click click click... Good leg, good leg, good leg!
Eh, oke.
Uhm, okay.
Sekarang, uh, udah bisa... udah bisa berdiri. I can stand now.
Now, uh, I can... I can stand up. I can stand now.
Now, about my other arm... Ah, there it is.
Istirahat. Sembunyikan tangan itu.
Rest. Hide those hands.
Ollie! Seperti baru lagi. Hehe.
Ollie! Like brand new again. Hehe.
It's because of that... di... I don't know what to call her.
Ollie kan tadi tahu ikutan harus bilang apa,
Ollie knew what to say earlier,
ada maling tiba-tiba.
a thief suddenly appeared.
Maaf, kono dorobou neneko-san,
Sorry, this cat burglar-chan,
mah, mau udah enggak apa-apa kan ya? Udah enggak ada, jadi seharusnya udah enggak apa-apa kan ya?
well, it's alright now, right? It's gone, so it should be fine now, right?
Mo ancin-ancin.
Mo anshin-anshin.
Apa? Moshimoshi? Haheng?
What? Moshimoshi? Haheng?
Haheng? Haheng? Haheng? Jangan-jangan ini? Haheng?
Haheng? Haheng? Haheng? Don't tell me this? Haheng?
Bisa-bisanya ngelesain haheng enggak?
How can you brush off haheng?
Mualas.
So lazy.
Mau sama dateng.
Wanting to come too.
Yeay! Ollie! Silakan perkenalkan diri.
Yay! Ollie! Please introduce yourself.
Halo, aku Ayunda Risu, Hololive ID Generation 1.
Hello, I am Ayunda Risu, Hololive ID Generation 1.
Kemudian ada Pipi, yo Pipi, yo Pipi Not Lo-Fi, hello.
Then there's Pipi, yo Pipi, yo Pipi Not Lo-Fi, hello.
Yeah, welcome to IDat-to Melission.
Ollie, nanti kamu jangan lihat Twitter ya. Eh ada apa? Ada apa dengan Twitter?
Ollie, don't look at Twitter later. Eh, what is it? What's up with Twitter?
Jangan lihat Twitter, enggak apa-apa. Jangan lihat Twitter berdua, jangan.
Don't look at Twitter, it's fine. Don't look at Twitter together, don't.
Mumpung nih kalian di sini, while you guys are still here.
Since you guys are here, while you guys are still here.
Enak nih kita main enggak sih? I think it's fun if we play.
Wouldn't it be fun if we play? I think it's fun if we play.
Boleh? Ya guys?
Can we? Right guys?
Aturan mainnya, jangan ada yang berdosa, tidak boleh berkata kasar.
The rule is, no sinning, no swearing.
Kalau gitu, mari kita main charades game, let's play some charades.
If so, let's play a charades game, let's play some charades.
Jadi rules-nya simpel ya, Ollie akan memperagakan sesuatu, kalian harus menebak apabila benar, kalian boleh nge-request apapun dari Ollie.
So the rules are simple, Ollie will act something out, you guys have to guess if it's correct, you can request anything from Ollie.
Apapun? Apapun? Aduh mikirin apa nih? Apapun.
Anything? Anything? Ugh, what to think about? Anything.
Kamu yakin bisa, Yopi? Nah ini teman-teman nih.
Are you sure you can, Yopi? Well, these are friends.
Ini kan gara-gara di-set-nya di chat pada nulis malas semua, malas.
This is because everyone in chat wrote lazy, lazy.
Ya udah jangan malas-malas lagi ya kalau bisa jangan malas. Enggak boleh, enggak boleh malas.
Okay then, don't be lazy anymore if possible, don't be lazy. You can't, you can't be lazy.
Kalau gitu kita langsung ke pertanyaan pertama kali ya, heeh. Ngoki? Oke kalau gitu pertanyaan pertama.
If so let's go straight to the first question, yeah. Okay? Okay then, first question.
Itu. Setato!
That. Start!
Mudah ya? Mudah kan?
Easy right? Easy right?
Harusnya aku yang jawab.
Should be me answering.
Anda kalah cepat.
You're too slow.
Kalau gitu, apakah ada otoku sebentar? Ini mumpung nih, mumpung banget.
If so, is there otoku for a moment? Since we have the chance, really the chance.
Kayak-nya kalau Ollie berpose memakai sesuatu yang keren, keren juga enggak sih?
It feels like if Ollie poses wearing something cool, is it cool too?
Boleh. Ollie ambil pistol dulu ya.
Sure. Ollie will grab a pistol first.
Buat melawan ini tadi, apa? Dorobou.
To fight this earlier, what? Dorobou.
Iya, ada Mozambique.
Yeah, there's Mozambique.
Keren enggak? Mau pose pakai ini kali ya.
Cool right? Want to use this pose maybe.
Kalau gitu, Yopi ada request enggak?
If so, Yopi, do you have a request?
Ini dari kamu jalannya ke belakang terus langsung balikkin badan ke sini gitu loh.
You walk backwards and then immediately turn your body back here like that.
Tuh kan, set. Pling! Wah itu kah.
See, set. Pling! Wow, that's it.
Tembak matiku, Kakak.
Shoot me to death, Big Sis.
Cidar-cidar! Prar-prar!
Bang-bang! Pow-pow!
Kalau gitu berikutnya Ollie juga bakal pakai ini kali ya.
If so, next Ollie will probably use this too.
Oke, kalau gitu kita langsung ke pertanyaan kedua.
Okay, if so let's go straight to the second question.
Oke. Setato!
Okay. Start!
Melihat, melihat. Bukan bukan bukan.
Seeing, seeing. No no no.
Kecil, Annya.
Small, Annya.
Pating gobor.
Scattered everywhere.
Mengelus kepala.
Stroke the head.
Apa sih?
What is this?
Pendek!
Short!
Ah?
Huh?
Terlalu pendek!
Too short!
Ke-hang.
Hanging?
Apa sih?
What is this?
Kecil, di-pet-pet, obo-, pendek!
Small, chubby, short!
Apa?
What?
Tinggi! Tinggi! Tinggi!
Tall! Tall! Tall!
Hah?
Huh?
Ini tuh apa?
What is this?
Apa sih?
Komentar, jangan ada-ada yang debat terus.
Comments, stop having debates.
Enggak sampai, kayaknya belum ada yang, ah.
Not reaching, looks like no one's, ah.
Yopi!
Enggak sampai! Terlalu pendek!
Didn't reach! Too short!
Theme
Alien
Theme: Alien
Ini UFO.
This is a UFO.
Eh, sebentar. Yang pendek bukan saya juga ya?
Wait, I'm not the short one either, right?
Aku sudah 50.
I'm already 50.
Ah, pendek.
Ah, short.
Berisik. Udah gitu aja, senpai, mau apa?
Noisy. Just like that, senpai, what do you want?
Mau minta pose apa ya?
What kind of pose should I ask for?
Kayak kamu tuh apa ya? Tangannya tuh diletakin di depan bibir gitu, terus tangan satu lagi ke belakang...
Like yours, hands placed in front of your lips like that, then another hand behind...
...kayak pose, pose cute-cute gitu loh.
...like a cute pose like that.
Ah, iya, um, gitu, terus badannya agak maju dikit ke depan, um, gitu.
Ah, yeah, um, like that, then your body moves forward a little bit, um, like that.
Gini?
Like this?
Ah, kawaii!
Keren! Oh, Taskaru.
Cool! Oh, Taskaru.
Tapi di belakangnya ada pistol, gimana ya?
But there's a pistol on the back, how is it?
Enggak apa-apa, enggak apa-apa.
It's fine, it's fine.
Shoot a bullet through my heart lah ya.
Shoot a bullet through my heart, huh.
Keren, keren, keren.
Cool, cool, cool.
Kalau gitu, ini yang terakhir ya.
If so, this is the last one.
Sip, kalau gitu yang terakhir, satu!
Great, then the last one, one!
Theme
Idol
Theme: Idol
Keren, keren, keren. Bener sekali, kalian berdua jago ya.
Cool, cool, cool. That's right, you two are good.
Iya nih. Ollie yang terlalu jago mendemonstrasikan.
That's right. Ollie is too good at demonstrating.
Nah, posenya apa ya? Unicorn!
Now, what's the pose? Unicorn pose!
jadi tuh pistolnya jadi tanduk gitu...
So the pistol becomes a horn...
Kenapa sih? Bawa kamera buka-bukaan, ini posenya...
Why? Bringing an open camera, this pose...
Unicorn! Unicorn tuh kayak gini. Nih, ku-letakkin nih.
Unicorn! Unicorn is like this. Here, I'm putting it down.
Menjijikan. Ya udah, kalau begitu, terima kasih teman-teman sudah datang.
Disgusting. Alright then, thank you friends for coming.
Hayo! Nonton sampai akhir ya!
Hey! Watch until the end, okay!
Oke, kita nonton dari kursi-kursi VIP di sini.
Okay, we're watching from the VIP seats here.
Iya nih. Keren ya? Thank you. Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
That's right. Cool, right? Thank you. Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Nih, ketek-ketek-ketek.
Here, armpits, armpits, armpits.
Memang, itu dua rada... rada miring ya?
Indeed, those two are a bit... a bit tilted, huh?
Mau sombek-nya.
Want the sombek.
Kalau begitu, teman-teman jangan lupa loh kalian pakai hashtag-nya Ollie lah, hashtag #KureijiOllie3D.
If so, guys don't forget to use Ollie's hashtag, #KureijiOllie3D.
Don't forget to use my hashtag by the way, guys.
Make it trend in Twitter, that'd be pretty cool.
Oh, banner juga ya, so, gua meeting?
Oh, banner too, so, I'm meeting?
Halo? Mosi-mosi? Halo? Loh?
Hello? Moshi-mosi? Hello? Huh?
Ada suara? Halo, halo, halo! Ollie super kawaii password-nya!
There's sound? Hello, hello, hello! Ollie super kawaii is the password!
Kapan murah, mantap, crazy! Apa-apaan Ananda?
Cheap when, awesome, crazy! What is this, Ananda?
Halo, selamat datang yang tiga ya! Rahmat, Omnitrix, Furball!
Hello, welcome the three of you! Rahmat, Omnitrix, Furball!
Yay! Selamat datang!
Yay! Welcome!
Wih, aduh, aku dibilang senpai, aku diselametin, jadi senang Ollie!
Wow, man, I'm called senpai, I'm congratulated, Ollie is so happy!
Ramen? Gimana nih? Mana ramennya? Enggak ada buat kalian.
Ramen? How is this? Where's the ramen? There's none for you guys.
Kalian di sini tuh bukan buat ramen, tahu enggak sih? Kalian di sini tuh buat main game.
You guys are here not for ramen, you know? You guys are here to play games.
No way, aku di-scam. Tadi kata Kaila, 'Ayo Kubu ikut makan ramen gratis!'
No way, I got scammed. Earlier Kaila said, 'Come on Kubu, join and eat free ramen!'
Berarti kalau main game, hadiahnya dapat ramen? Hadiahnya dapat pos gratis ya, bukan ramen ya?
So if you play games, the prize is ramen? The prize is free postage, right, not ramen?
Mohon, hoax-nya jangan disebarluaskan, utuhnya makan pos gratis dan ramen. Oke deh kalau gitu.
Please don't spread the hoax, the truth is eating free postage and ramen. Okay then if so.
Kalau gitu kita bakal main series. Kalian tahukan peraturannya?
If so, we're gonna play Series. You guys know the rules?
Ya sudah, tahu, tahu, tahu. Kalau gitu kita langsung play saja kali ya.
Alright, know, know, know. If so let's just play right away.
Skip sedikit tutorial.
Skip the tutorial a bit.
Ombak. Kalau gitu drum! Belum, belum, belum, belum.
Waves. If so, drums! Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Kita mulai ya. Kalau gitu start!
We'll start. If so, start!
Astaga.
Good grief.
Berpikir. Nongki-nongki, buang air besar.
Thinking. Hanging out, taking a dump.
Lu, berapa, tau?
How many are you, you know?
Sumo?
Sumo? Wah, keren nih. Di chat udah pada langsung betul loh.
Sumo? That's cool. The chat got it right instantly.
Jongkok?
Squatting?
Bukan, apa ya? Yago...
No, what is it? Ya...
Yagoo? Yang posenya kayak gini?
Yagoo? The one whose pose is like this?
Yang fotonya hitam putih itu loh. Benar, benar, benar. Yang fotonya hitam putih.
The one whose photo is in black and white. Right, right, right. The one with the black and white photo.
Kalau begitu, Zeta, Anda bisa minta request? Ah, tapi sebelumnya minta.
In that case, Zeta, could you make a request? Ah, but before that, ask.
Olli ingin mengambil sesuatu yang keren. Nanti ya!
Olli wants to grab something cool. Hang on!
Apa, apa, guys? Berunding dulu. Aku belum siap.
What, what, guys? Let's confer first. I'm not ready.
Tau, apa ya, aku mau... Cepat! Curi ramen dari kepala nih.
You know, what is it, I want to... Quick! Steal the ramen from her head.
Eh, kenapa? Keren enggak? Curi ramen nih.
Eh, why? Is it cool? Stealing the ramen.
Weh, gendang. Apaan? Kebucetnya dari kepala asli loh. Dari itu, ini.
Whoa, eardrum. What? The bucket is from her actual head. From that, this.
Beneran, barusan. Coba lihat, coba lihat magic enggak nih? Bukan sulap bukan sihir ya.
Seriously, just now. Look, look, is that magic? No tricks or magic, y'know.
Boleh, mana-mana? Bukan sulap bukan... Oke, oke, apa tuh?
Sure, where-where? Not magic... Okay, okay, what's that?
Set, pan, zai!
Bo- Wow! Keren banget!
Bo- Wow! That's so cool!
Keren kan? Gila, keren banget.
Cool, right? Crazy, it's so cool.
Jadi minrou! Widih!
Now it's a minrou! Whoa!
Kalau gitu, ada request pose apa? Kalau potong kaki pakai pedangnya bisa enggak?
In that case, what pose do you request? Can you use the sword to cut your legs?
Astaga, lu brutal banget!
Good grief, you're so brutal!
Apa enggak ada yang lain gitu?
Is there nothing else?
Eh, ini, aku mau pose Excalibur.
Eh, this, I want an Excalibur pose.
Excalibur. Oh, kalau gitu, Excalibur. Ini kan ya? Bentar.
Excalibur. Oh, in that case, Excalibur. This, right? Wait.
Duh, berat ya. Kayak gini ya?
Man, it's heavy. Like this?
Iya, iya, benar, benar, benar. Dicabut. Dicabut.
Yes, yes, right, right, right. Pull it out. Pull it out.
Wah! Pink, pink, shing, shing, shing, shing!
Whoa! Pink, pink, shing, shing, shing, shing!
Keren enggak nih? Keren, keren, keren, keren.
Isn't this cool? Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Kalau gitu kita ke, ini ya, pertanyaan berikutnya. Mau, mau, mau, mau.
In that case, let's move to, um, the next question. Want, want, want, want.
Oke, oke, wah. Ayo, jangan kalah. Sato! Iya, iya, iya, iya, iya.
Okay, okay, wow. Come on, don't lose. Sato! Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ini sulit ya? Eh, sulit. Sulit, sulit, sulit.
This is difficult, huh? Eh, difficult. Difficult, difficult, difficult.
Kodok? Bukan, ini, Angga, Angga, Angga!
Frog? No, this, Angga, Angga, Angga!
Kepiting, kepiting! Bukan, bukan, bukan. Kalau gitu ini deh.
Crab, crab! No, no, no. In that case, this one.
Apa namanya? Eh, stretching.
What's it called? Um, stretching.
Pemanasan olahraga, akrobat, pesenam, SKJ.
Sports warming-up, acrobat, gymnast, SKJ.
Itu, itu di chat udah ada yang hampir... Oh, udah ada yang benar. Aku lihat chat.
That, that in the chat already almost... Oh, someone got it right. I'm checking the chat.
Kalau begitu, marin, Seijo, marin, tidur, terjatuh.
In that case, marin, Seijo, marin, sleep, falling down.
Oh, itu termasuk betul deh. Jawabannya Pirate!
Oh, that counts as correct, huh. The answer is Pirate!
Bajak laut? Aku enggak nyontek sama sekali kok!
Pirate? I didn't cheat at all!
Oke. Dari tadi...
Okay. Since earlier...
Oke, oke, oke. Ya udah, aku mau menghukum.
Okay, okay, okay. Fine, I'm going to punish.
Request, bukan hukum. Loh, kenapa enggak hukum? Request.
Request, not punishment. Why isn't it a punishment? Request.
Eh, boleh, boleh. Roleplay boleh enggak nge-roleplay gitu? Oke, gimana, gimana?
Eh, sure, sure. Is roleplay okay, like roleplaying? Okay, how, how?
Oke, kamu sekarang ke dapur, terus kamu motong bawang, bawang, bawang, bawang bombay atau bawang apa kek, bikin ramen tapi pakai pisau itu.
Okay, you go to the kitchen now, and then you cut onions, onions, onions, onions, bombay onions or whatever, make ramen but using that knife.
Aku pengen ke dapur cuman males, di sini aja ya, aku roleplay.
I want to go to the kitchen but I'm lazy, right here, I'll roleplay.
Oh ya udah, boleh, boleh, boleh, cuman motong aja.
Oh alright, sure, sure, sure, just cutting.
Motong sambil kayak, kayak ceritanya ada ini, ada costumer, kayak, 'Eh, mau pesan apa?' Kayak gitu-gitu.
Cutting while like, like the story has this, a customer, like, "Eh, what do you want to order?" Something like that.
Oke. 'Silakan, silakan, mau nyicip apa?' 'Oh, iya nih, miso, miso, iya nih.'
Okay. "Please, please, what would you like to taste?" "Oh, yeah, miso, miso, yeah."
Nah, yang dramatis, yang dramatis terus! Hah, yang lebih dramatis!
Now, more dramatic, more dramatic! Ha, even more dramatic!
Selawat datang kepada ramen shop saya, ingin makan apakah anda? Tahukah kalian kalau daun bawang itu sangat baik untuk kesehatan anda?
Welcome to my ramen shop, what would you like to eat? Do you know that scallions are very good for your health?
Gila, semacam ngiklan. Udah deh.
Crazy, kind of like an advertisement. That's enough.
Oke, okelah, okelah, okelah, aduh, malu gua.
Okay, fine, fine, fine, gosh, I'm embarrassed.
Kalau gitu ini yang terakhir ya. Kayak, ayo bisa. Ayo Kaila, ayo Kaila, ayo Kaila.
In that case, this is the last one. Like, come on you can do it. Come on Kaila, come on Kaila, come on Kaila.
Ayo Kaila, aku bantu. Ya, aku juga bantu.
Come on Kaila, I'll help. Yeah, I'll help too.
Kalau bantu, aku juga bantu, aku paling membantu.
If you help, I'll help too, I help the most.
Ini, ini sulit. Sulit. Bukan.
This, this is difficult. Difficult. No.
Bukan beneran sulit sih. Menjaga keseimbangan. Bukan. Itu, itu, coba jawab, pemirsa.
Not really difficult though. Maintaining balance. No. That, that, try answering, viewers.
Ipus, ikan pesutlah, ikan pesut.
Ipus, Irrawaddy dolphin, Irrawaddy dolphin.
Ikan pesut.
Irrawaddy dolphin.
Super, super, super hero, superhero.
Eh, kok, apa Yagoo ya? Superhero, Kela, itu Kela yang jawab itu, Kela yang jawab. Oh, Kela jawab itu. Iya, iya Kela yang jawab itu.
Eh, why, is it Yagoo? Superhero, Kela, that's Kela who answered, Kela answered. Oh, Kela answered that. Yeah, yeah Kela answered that.
Oh, sorry, sorry kalau gitu, ripp.
Oh, sorry, sorry in that case, ripp.
Iya, iya mirip emang. Ayo hukum, kesalah, hukum lah, hukum lah, hukum lah.
Yeah, yeah it looks similar indeed. Come on punish, mistake, punish him, punish him, punish him.
Loh, jangan dihukum dong. Apa ya?
Hey, don't punish him. What is it?
Aduh, apa ya?
Gosh, what is it?
Emodi-emodi gen-hukuman, masa sih?
Emotional punishments? Seriously?
Ya udah, kalau kalau gitu, itu pose paling sundere kalau gitu.
Well, if that's the case, that's the most tsundere pose.
Bukan ya bawa pedang gitu ya?
Isn't it like holding a sword?
Seram ya?
Scary, right?
Bukan, kamu tuh suka sama kamu ya? Ya, tsundere ya?
No, it's like 'I like you,' tsundere-style, right?
Tapi bukan karena kamu nggak suka, jangan salah ya.
Not because you don't like it, don't get me wrong!
Buttobasu yo!
I'll beat you up!
Sangat-sangat mendalami peran sekali.
Really getting into character.
Iya, suka-suka mau, mau, oh, Iga shimasu!
Yeah, whatever you want, Iga shimasu!
Tadi serah, makasih. Ya udah datang, aduh, repot-repot.
Thanks for earlier. Thanks for coming, oh, you went to all this trouble.
Pedangnya disimpan aja. Nanti ku-sita. Bye-bye, Senpai!
Just put the sword away. I'll confiscate it later. Bye-bye, Senpai!
Ayo, ayo, ambil ramen-nya jangan diambil!
Hey, hey, don't take the ramen!
Nah, barusan adalah gen 3. Tunggu, ini Ollie tertusuk lagi kepala Ollie kali ya? Coba nantikan ya.
Now, that was Gen 3. Wait, is Ollie getting stabbed in the head again? Look forward to it.
Ketan-cup, ketan-cup lagi. Mau, eh, kencan, ken-kencan ya? Kalau gitu kan tadi udah ada gen 1.
Date, another date. Want to, uh, date? Well, we already had Gen 1 earlier.
Udah ada gen 3, berarti seharusnya ada gen 1 lagi sih. There should be like one more gen, right?
We had Gen 3, so there should be another Gen 1, right? There should be like one more gen, right?
Mosi-mosi? Eh, alu-alu, alu-alu, alu, alu-alu. Kok serem ya, siapa ya?
Moshi moshi? Uh, hello, hello... Why is this so creepy, who is it?
Kayak-kayaknya aku tadi mendengar ada seseorang yang mencurigakan.
It sounds like I just heard someone suspicious.
Enggak, enggak, siapa sih?
No, no, who could it be?
Heh, horror loh. Siap-siap, ini.
Hey, it's horror. Get ready for this.
Halo, aku adalah... Attention please! I am Pavolia Reine dari ID generasi 2.
Hello, I am... Attention please! I am Pavolia Reine from ID Generation 2.
Halo, eh bukan, ini Melubisa jadi Hoshimachi ID generasi 2. I don't talk like that. Itu eh Hoshimachi Suisei-senkan ya?
Hello, wait no, Melubisa becomes Hoshimachi ID Generation 2. I don't talk like that. Is that Hoshimachi Suisei's battleship?
Miriw-miriw tuh, oh my god, apa?
It looks similar, oh my god, what?
Woi, udah-udah-udah. Lu tekan-tekan-tekan. Kalau kalian pengen pose lagi, kalian harus main game.
Hey, stop already. You keep pressing it. If you guys want to pose again, you have to play a game.
Game apa tuh? Apakah main Surreys? Kita bakal playingister games.
What kind of game? Playing Surreys? We'll be playing Mister Games.
Kalau kalian bener-bener baru game ya. Aku sih kayaknya jago banget nggak sih main ini? Aku mau pokoknya aku udah kepikiran mau request Ollie mau main apa. Masa? Ya udah kalau gitu kita langsung masuk aja nih ya.
If you guys are really new to games. I think I'm really good at this, right? I already have in mind what I want to request Ollie to play. Really? Well then, let's just jump right into it.
Okee, undian pertama! Stop!
Okay, first draw! Stop!
Zombie! Let's go!
Kalau gitu, aduh, biar biar seru nih, kan dari tadi Ollie sendiri kan ya? Ollie panggil temen dulu kali ya, biar bisa pose bareng.
If that's the case, uh, to make it fun, since Ollie's been alone so far, should I call a friend so we can pose together?
Siapa ya? Siapa ya? Cepat tuh, cepat tuh. Woi!
Who could it be? Who could it be? Hurry up, hurry up. Hey!
Aku ditendang-ditendang diteriakin.
I got kicked and yelled at.
Ini-ini. Jadi nanti Ollie bakal pose sama Udin. Gemesin banget.
This one. So later Ollie will pose with Udin. So adorable.
Muter-muter, tuur.
Spinning around, tuur.
Woi, woi, wah gue nge-bor. Hanya untuk Tante. Aduh, makasih banget nge-bor banget sih.
Hey, hey, wow I'm drilling. Just for Auntie. Wow, thanks so much for drilling so hard.
Kalau gitu ada request apa nih, Renet? 'Aku mau kamu kayak, kamu tahu nggak sih kalau orang tuh dance off gitu, aku mau kamu sama Udin kayak work off gitu loh.'
So what's the request, Renet? 'I want you like, you know when people do a dance off, I want you and Udin to kind of work off like that.'
Random ya apa. Ding, lu bisa, ya udah lu ditantang tuh.
Random or whatever. Ding, you can, well you're challenged.
Akan kita coba. Kalau gitu, ayo kita lihat siapa yang paling jago. Ya pasti saya dong.
We'll try it. If so, let's see who's the best. It's definitely me, right?
Sit sit sit sit. Ini pantat aku kelihatan agak sedih ya. Nggak apa-apa ada kayak dikipasin wesu-wesu. Dikipasin makin gerak ya? Iya betul banget.
Sit sit sit sit. My butt looks kind of sad here. It's fine with some fanning. Fanning makes it move more, right? Yeah, exactly.
Wah, seru banget. Wah, seru banget. Waduh, sepertinya seperti deja vu gitu deh. Mohon maaf.
Wow, so much fun. Wow, so much fun. Whoa, it feels like deja vu. I apologize.
Teraskar, terima kasih. Terima kasih.
Teraskar, thank you. Thank you.
Yuk, kita langsung aja kali ya. Ini yang terakhir kali ya, satu buat Anya gitu. Anya, semangat! Oke, siap.
Let's just go straight into it. This is the last one, right? One for Anya. Anya, spirit! Okay, ready.
Eh, ini susah ya. Din, bantu gua, Din. Buat aku sendiri ya.
Uh, this is hard. Din, help me out, Din. Do it for me, okay?
Kan kamu pro-nya, bisalah. Gitu. Emang ngapain?
You're the pro, you can do it. Like that. What are you even doing?
Menyihir. Oke, puppet master itu.
Casting spells. Okay, that puppet master.
Eh?
Game Master, Game Master.
Lucu banget.
So cute!
Iya, kalau gitu, ada request-nya apa?
Yeah, if so, what are your requests?
Oh iya, kamu sama Udin, mumpung Udin ada di sini...
Oh yeah, you and Udin, since Udin is here...
Eh, aku pengen lihat kalian pancho, bisa enggak sih?
Uh, I want to see if you guys can do 'pancho', can you?
Bisa enggak? Din, kita pengen lihat kalian pancho, aduh pancho gitu bisa...
Can you? Din, we want to see you guys do pancho, oh pancho like that...
Bisa enggak?
Can you?
Kita... Kita gandengan aja deh!
We... Let's just hold hands!
Pancho...
Kita gandengan aja, enggak apa-apa, Teteh.
Let's just hold hands, it's fine, Teteh.
Eh, lu pendek sih, Teteh.
Hey, you're short, Teteh.
Eh, kayak gini!
Eh, like this!
Teteh!
Teteh, tapi aku enggak punya...
Teteh, but I don't...
Bilangnya Teteh.
You called me Teteh.
Bukan aku yang bilang!
I wasn't the one who said it!
Aku sadar diri kok, tidak apa-apa.
I'm self-aware, it's fine.
Kalau begitu, makasih! Aduh, hariku tersayang!
If so, thanks! Oh, dearest day of mine!
Selamat jalan, Teteh!
Farewell, Teteh!
No motion for the 3D!
Jangan-jangan pengen menonton!
Don't tell me you want to watch!
Jangan lupa kalian enggak duit pakai hashtag ini dong!
Don't forget to use this hashtag when tweeting!
Undur, tidak pasti dong.
Unsure, not for sure.
Susu stroberi yang di fountain, kamu boleh enggak?
Strawberry milk at the fountain, can you?
Oke, sip!
Okay, great!
Oke banget, oke banget.
Super great, super great.
Kalau gitu, bye-bye!
If so, bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Semangat!
Bye-bye! Keep it up!
Thank you! Miyabi!
Wah, barusan adalah teman-teman Ollie dari HoloID. Ya kan, Din? Syurga!
Wow, that just now was Ollie's friends from HoloID. Right, Din? Heaven!
Parasengklak padakan?
Heeh, emang.
Yeah, indeed.
Gitulah, ada apa tuh di chat? Eh, kalian cepat banget, Ollie cuma bisa baca Taskarulo aja.
That's how it is, what's in the chat? Eh, you guys are so fast, Ollie can only read Taskarulo.
Kalau gitu, sebenarnya masih ada banyak nih, teman-teman, a few more things that we want to show you, so don't go anywhere, don't go anywhere manakah.
If so, actually there are still a lot of these, friends, a few more things that we want to show you, so don't go anywhere, don't go anywhere.
Eh, kono ato wa mada, ipai-ipai aru yo. Dakara ne, eto, suite...
Eh, after this, there's still lots more. So, uh, suite...
Koyou! Let's go!
Come on! Let's go!
Pemirsa, selepas ini kita akan mengasih kalian tutorial caranya untuk bikin sikat miring.
Viewers, after this we are going to give you a tutorial on how to make a slanted brush.
Ya, kalau kalian pengen sikat piring, sudah pasti awalnya harus kita sanggupin.
Yeah, if you want a slanted brush, surely the first thing we must be able to do is endure it.
Ya, kan? Kalau kalian enggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
Right? If you can't endure it, then endure it!
Kalau niat kalian sudah bulat, kalau gitu ini, niatnya itu kita lempar ke atas.
If your intention is already firm, then this, the intention we throw upwards.
Kemudian kita gondol sayang.
Then we carry it, dear.
Nah, ini kalau gondol sayang udah harus miring ya, diagonal ya, teman-teman, 45 derajat.
Now, if it's carrying it, dear, it already has to be slanted, diagonal, friends, 45 degrees.
Nah, kalau udah sampai sini, berikutnya kalian ingin...
Now, once it's up to here, next you want to...
Dong! Ketum!
Nah, di sini pun kalian harus cuman gitu loh, harus ada asmaranya.
Now, here too you just have to be like that, there must be romance in it.
Setelah kalian sudah sampai sini, kalian pengen dong iris tipis.
After you've reached here, you want to slice it thinly.
Ini tipis-tipis tuh, sot tipis-tipisnya mungkin ya guys, kayak lagi masak gitu.
This is thin, thin, the thinnest maybe guys, like you're cooking.
Kalau udah kita dong potong manis. Nah, iya kan? Kalau kalian habis ngiris, pengen itu, pengen dicincang itu kan, makan, kita potong-potong.
If already we dong cut sweet. Right? If you've finished slicing, you want it, you want it chopped, you eat it, we cut it up.
Setelah kalian potong-potong, kita tinggal dong sikat miring.
After you cut it up, we just dong slanted brush.
Nah, tuh, Udin nanti bisa. Apakah kalian bisa mengikutinya juga?
Now, look, Udin can do it later. Can you follow along too?
Jadi kalau kita gabungin semua ya, teman-teman, tolong ikuti tutorial ini dengan baik.
So if we combine all of them, friends, please follow this tutorial well.
Mari kita mulai.
Let's start.
Pertama, kalau enggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
First, if you can't endure it, then endure it!
Lempar niatnya!
Throw your intention!
Gondol sayang!
Carry it, dear!
Dong!
Gondol ketum!
Carry ketum!
Nah!
Now!
Kemudian kita iris tipis!
Then we slice thinly!
Todododododong! Potong manis!
Todododododong! Cut sweet!
Sat!
Nah, Udin tahu berikutnya apa? Sikat miring!
Now, Udin knows what's next? Slanted brush!
Ya, sama teman-teman, kalian baru saja menghabiskan 1 menit kalian tidak melakukan hal yang berguna. Sekian, mari kita ke scene yang berikutnya.
Yeah, friends, you just spent 1 minute of your time not doing anything useful. That's all, let's go to the next scene.
Pemirsa, selepas ini kita akan mengasih kalian tutorial caranya untuk bikin sikat miring.
Viewers, after this we are going to give you a tutorial on how to make a slanted brush.
Ya, kalau kalian pengen sikat piring, sudah pasti awalnya harus kita sanggupin.
Yeah, if you want a slanted brush, surely the first thing we must be able to do is endure it.
Ya, kan? Kalau kalian enggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
Right? If you can't endure it, then endure it!
Kalau niat kalian sudah bulat, kalau gitu ini, niatnya itu kita lempar ke atas.
If your intention is already firm, then this, the intention we throw upwards.
Kemudian kita gondol sayang.
Then we carry it, dear.
Nah, ini kalau gondol sayang udah harus miring ya, diagonal ya, teman-teman, 45 derajat.
Now, if it's carrying it, dear, it already has to be slanted, diagonal, friends, 45 degrees.
Nah, kalau udah sampai sini, berikutnya kalian ingin...
Now, once it's up to here, next you want to...
Dong! Ketum!
Nah, di sini pun kalian harus cuman gitu loh, harus ada asmaranya.
Now, here too you just have to be like that, there must be romance in it.
Setelah kalian sudah sampai sini, kalian pengen dong iris tipis.
After you've reached here, you want to slice it thinly.
Ini tipis-tipis tuh, sot tipis-tipisnya mungkin ya guys, kayak lagi masak gitu.
This is thin, thin, the thinnest maybe guys, like you're cooking.
Kalau udah kita dong potong manis. Nah, iya kan? Kalau kalian habis ngiris, pengen itu, pengen dicincang itu kan, makan, kita potong-potong.
If already we dong cut sweet. Right? If you've finished slicing, you want it, you want it chopped, you eat it, we cut it up.
Setelah kalian potong-potong, kita tinggal dong sikat miring.
After you cut it up, we just dong slanted brush.
Nah, tuh, Udin nanti bisa. Apakah kalian bisa mengikutinya juga?
Now, look, Udin can do it later. Can you follow along too?
Jadi kalau kita gabungin semua ya, teman-teman, tolong ikuti tutorial ini dengan baik.
So if we combine all of them, friends, please follow this tutorial well.
Mari kita mulai.
Let's start.
Pertama, kalau enggak sanggup, ya sanggupin!
First, if you can't endure it, then endure it!
Lempar niatnya!
Throw your intention!
Gondol sayang!
Carry it, dear!
Dong!
Dengerin, dengerin!
Listen, listen!
Nih, nih, kita... Hihihihi!
Here, here, we... Hehehehe!
Bener-bener nih, kalian baru saja tertawa, berkurangnya apa?
Seriously, you guys just laughed, what's missing?
Singkatnya,
In short,
Ya, sama-sama, teman-teman, kalian baru saja menghabiskan satu menit kalian tidak melakukan hal yang berguna.
Yeah, you guys just spent one minute of your time doing nothing useful.
Sekian, mari kita ke scene yang berikutnya.
That's all, let's move on to the next scene.
Dengarkanlah suaraku
Listen to my voice,
id:entity
Berdiri di tengah terangnya kilau cahaya
Standing in the middle of the bright glittering light,
Ohayou! Konbanwa! Kami serukan kepada dunia
Ohayou! Konbanwa! We call out to the world,
Mengudara 'tuk hari ini
Broadcasting for today,
Bagian dari diri yang manakah yang harus kutunjukkan?
Which part of myself should I show?
'Ku tak dapat pernah memutuskan
I could never decide,
Lalu suatu hari pesan-pesan berdatangan
Then one day, messages started coming in,
Kata-kata perih membuatku kehilangan arah
Hurtful words made me lose my way,
Senyuman di balik layar, sanggupkah untuk 'kupertahankan?
Can I maintain the smile behind the screen?
Tak pernah ingin kecewakan siapapun di luar sana
Never wanting to disappoint anyone out there,
Namun di saat banyaknya suara, manakah yang 'ku harus dengar?
But amidst all the voices, which one should I listen to?
Mencoba mendengarkan suara di dalam hati
Trying to listen to the voice within my heart,
Inilah diri yang ingin 'ku selalu tunjukkan, berbagai suara yang berpadu
This is the self I always want to show, various voices blending together,
Dan menjadi satu, id:entity
And becoming one, id:entity
Hari-hari berlalu dan sekarang 'ku di sini
Days passed by and now I'm here,
Berdiri di tepi panggung ini, menyambut dunia
Standing at the edge of this stage, welcoming the world,
Tetapi 'ku tak sendiri
But I'm not alone,
Bersama lainnya sekarang, seakan seperti keluarga, bersatu dalam perbedaan
Together with others now, feeling like family, united in differences,
Namun di saat banyaknya perbedaan
Yet amidst so many differences,
Dapatkah harmoni tercipta?
Can harmony be created?
Bergandengan tangan berjuang raih mimpi bersama
Holding hands, striving to achieve dreams together,
Semua bersorak dengan suara gempita
Everyone cheering with a roaring voice,
Menyebarkan kebahagiaan, di mana pun itu, bergemalah
Spreading happiness, wherever it may be, echoing,
Panggung yang lebih besar kini menunggu
A bigger stage is now waiting,
Waktunya telah tiba tanpa adanya ragu
The time has come without any doubt,
Dengan semua warna suara, menjadi harmoni sebenarnya
With all the colors of voices, becoming the true harmony,
Hilanglah semua rasa bimbang di hati
Disappear all doubts in the heart,
Inilah diri yang ingin 'ku selalu tunjukkan, berbagai suara yang berpadu
This is the self I always want to show, various voices blending together,
Dalam perbedaan takkan pernah tergoyahkan
In differences, it will never be shaken,
Dan menjadi satu, id:entity
And becoming one, id:entity
Ohayou! Konbanwa! Otsukaresama deshita!
Ohayou! Konbanwa! Good work today!
Ohayou! Konbanwa!
Kita 'kan jumpa lagi!
We'll meet again!
Capek... Haha, so tired! But that's okay!
Tired... Haha, so tired! But that's okay!
Capek tapi senang. Senang banget kan?
Tired, but happy. Really happy, right?
Dan... Apakah kalian melihat tadi? Tampilannya di mana? Menarik, kan?
And... did you guys see that earlier? Where was the display? Interesting, right?
Semangat, id:entity arena!
Keep it up, id:entity arena!
Ini song theme-nya juri, ya?
This is the jury's theme song, right?
Udah dengar belum? Udah pada belum? Udah pada dengar? Ollie guys, aku terlalu high!
Have you heard it yet? Have you all? Have you heard it? Ollie guys, I'm too high!
Senang banget, senang banget! Keren banget! Sumpah, Ollie! Uh-oh.
So happy, so happy! So cool! Swear, Ollie! Uh-oh.
Perasaan adalah identity voices, tapi bukan hanya itu, kita...
Feelings are identity voices, but not only that, we...
Ollie ada beberapa pengumuman nih, yang pertama namanya...
Ollie has a few announcements, first is...
I'm so excited! I buy for everyone! Ini dia merch yang Ollie siapkan buat kalian.
I'm so excited! I buy for everyone! This is the merch Ollie prepared for you guys.
Original merchandise yang kami siapin buat kalian. Udah karena minasan no...
The original merchandise we prepared for you. Because of everyone's...
Kami ini yoi shimashita. So, hingga ini dia, dong! The Super Kawaii Zombie Coach Jacket! Yeah!
We prepared this. So, ta-da! The Super Kawaii Zombie Coach Jacket! Yeah!
So, um... I noticed that most of my goods, not all of them are portable, guys. Semuanya portable enggak sih?
So, um... I noticed that most of my goods, not all of them are portable, guys. Are they all portable?
Danial ingin membuat sesuatu yang bisa kalian pakai, langsung kita bilang aja nih seragam kalian ya.
Daniel wanted to make something you guys can wear, let's just say these are your uniforms.
You guys can see it as your uniforms. So I worked real hard so that you guys can have this.
It's going to be really cool, ya? Yang aslinya jauh lebih keren. The real thing is a lot cooler than it is!
It's going to be really cool, right? The original is way cooler. The real thing is a lot cooler than it is!
Tutorial deh mutto kakoyokatta yo! Zezeyihi ne! Ini nanti bakal dijual berbarengan bersama mini live kita.
Tutorial de motto kakoyokatta yo! Zezeyihi ne! This will later be sold alongside our mini live.
After our mini live, this will be on sale, so make sure that you guys are ready in your pockets, ne! Online... e-bay-bay, buy... ne!
Hmm, kemudian ada satu lagi nih pengumuman, yaitu... ini, eh, hehe, eksklusif hanya untuk kalian yang nonton.
Hmm, then there's one more announcement, which is... this, eh, hehe, exclusively just for you guys watching.
Ollie akan bikin... game! It's a game, guys, creation Ollie ya!
Ollie will make... a game! It's a game, guys, Ollie's creation, yeah!
Untuk detailnya, nonton aja nanti sampai akhir stream!
For the details, just watch until the end of the stream!
If you guys want to know more about the details, make sure you watch until the end of the Ollie stream!
Oh, kemudian yang terakhir ada sesuatu yang... aduh, ini yang ini tuh... deg-degan, mau nangis belum.
Oh, and then lastly there's something... oh, this one... I'm nervous, about to cry.
Are you guys crying? Dan ingin Ollie sampaikan kepada kalian, aslinya ingin dari Monte Carlo, guys, itu ada kata-kata enggak?
Are you guys crying? And what Ollie wants to convey to you guys, originally from Monte Carlo, guys, is there any words?
Tolong dengarkan ya.
Please listen, okay.
Nah, um... actually Ollie sudah summed it up over here. Sebenarnya udah Ollie rangkum sih ya.
Now, um... actually Ollie already summed it up over here. Actually Ollie already summarized it.
Kata-katanya Ollie di sebelah sini. I kind of already have everything written out, but just so that we're in the same page...
Ollie's words are right over here. I kind of already have everything written out, but just so that we're on the same page...
I want to say thank you from the very bottom of my heart because, you know, if it weren't for you guys...
if you guys didn't give me a chance to get on this stage, I would have only been an undead.
Ollie mungkin enggak akan ada di sini dan berkat kalian Ollie juga tetap di sini. It's thanks to you guys that I'm still here.
Ollie might not have been here and thanks to you guys Ollie is still here too. It's thanks to you guys that I'm still here.
Itu, ne, minna no okage de Ollie wa koko ni tatte iru yo, honmani.
That, ne, thanks to everyone Ollie is standing right here, truly.
Jadi, agak emi, ya, it's a little bit emotional, but I really do mean it.
So, a bit emi, yeah, it's a little bit emotional, but I really do mean it.
I know it's a little bit cliché, I know you guys hear it a lot, but this comes for me personally...
Ini datang dari hati Ollie yang terdalam. Oleh karena itu, terima kasih banyak.
This comes from the deepest part of Ollie's heart. Therefore, thank you very much.
Itu, selalu support kurete, honmani arigatou gozaimashita.
That, for always supporting me, thank you very much truly.
Um, and again, I love you guys all so much. You guys mean the world to me, you guys never know.
So thank you very much.
Wah, emori na! Agak sediki-te, emosional ya dengan yang sebelum. Are you guys crying?
Wow, emotional! A bit little bit, emotional right with the previous. Are you guys crying?
Um, kalau gitu, ada satu lagi nih.
Um, in that case, there's one more.
Kalau belum itu, belum selesai, ga si? If we haven't sang that is not over yet, isn't it?
If that hasn't, hasn't finished yet, right? If we haven't sung that, it's not over yet, isn't it?
Arewa, mada aru yo! Minna shiteru? You guys know? Apakah kalian tahu?
That, there is still more! Everyone knows? You guys know? Do you guys know?
The last song! Of course, from the very first thing that I've ever produced myself!
クレイジー・ジョリー!!
Crazy Ollie!!
退屈な日常 このままでいいのか
Are you fine with this boring daily life?
通知待ってケータイ見てばかりで
Just waiting for notifications and looking at my phone,
ハート止まっていても心震わせたいの
Even if my heart stops, I want to make it tremble.
これからがshow time 歩きだしてこうか
From here on is show time, shall we start walking?
1,2,3で星を見つけて
Finding a star at 1, 2, 3,
4,5,6で君を見つけたの
Finding you at 4, 5, 6,
7,8,9で夢を見つめて
Gazing at a dream at 7, 8, 9...
(え、アタシ？)
(Oh, me?)
行くぞ！
Let's go!
ツギハギカラダに 溢れてくよ memory
Memories overflowing into my patched-up body...
ズキズキアタマに 特効薬の我爱你
A special remedy for my throbbing head, wǒ ài nǐ
つぎつぎ脳内に ぱぴりなmelody
Melodies popping one after another in my brain
うきうきなパーティー
An upbeat, exciting party
ARE YOU READY?
jollie jollie night ドレスコードなんてないの
Jollie jollie night, there is no dress code
shiny time is now 煌めいてくよ舞台
Shiny time is now, shining brightly on stage
crazy kureiji dance 心躍るようなジャーニー
Crazy Kureiji dance, a heart-throbbing journey
見つけたんだ とっておきの居場所
I found it, my absolute favorite place
LET'S GO!!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!! KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI SUPER!!
MEGA!! HYPER!! SISTER!! CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE
bad l lie なこともたまにあんだ
Sometimes bad lies happen too
sad l lie な雨が降ることもあんだ
And sometimes sad rain falls as well
だけど it's all right! いじける暇 no time!
But it's all right! No time to sulk!
これからが show time 虹がかかるよ!
From here on is show time, a rainbow will appear!
動悸がするくらい 今が好きなの
I love the present so much my heart pounds
時忘れるくらい 熱狂して万々歳
So absorbed I lose track of time, fanatical and overjoyed
体温上がってるトゥナイト bpmは上限無い
Temperature rising tonight, BPM has no upper limit
際限ないこの鬼才 皆に共有したい!
This limitless genius, I want to share with everyone!
アストロノーツ 満天のスターリー ナイト
Astronauts, a starry night across the full sky
泣く子 黙る 三千世界
The three-thousand worlds where crying children silence
主役 アタシ 以外に 無いじゃん？
Isn't the protagonist anyone other than me?
put your hands up ミュータント 集会
Put your hands up, mutant gathering
ミラーボール 反射する ブルーライト
Blue light reflecting off the mirror ball
アンサンブルで デンジャーじゃない？ 今夜は誰も 眠らせないの jolly jollie night
Isn't this ensemble dangerous? Tonight I won't let anyone sleep, jolly jollie night
徹頭徹尾 自信チャージして
Charging up my confidence from start to finish
一進一退 自陣 マージして
Merging my forces, advance and retreat
心の酸化 ➔ 還元 促進
Acidification of the heart -> reduction promotion
a to z 永久に！ なにちょっと 急停止!?
From A to Z forever! Wait, why a sudden stop!?
oh crazy!
ツギハギカラダに 繋がってく想い
Feelings connecting to my patched-up body
カチコチハートに 詰め込んだ願い
Wishes packed into my stiff heart
すぎすぎみんなに 消していくよ我爱你
Passing them on to everyone, erasing with wǒ ài nǐ
jollie jollie all i need kureiji party night!
ツギハギカラダに 溢れてくよ memory
Memories overflowing into my patched-up body...
ズキズキアタマに 特効薬の我爱你
A special remedy for my throbbing head, wǒ ài nǐ
つぎつぎ脳内に ぱぴりなmelody
Melodies popping one after another in my brain
うきうきなパーティー ARE YOU READY?
An upbeat party, ARE YOU READY?
jollie jollie night ドレスコードなんてないの
Jollie jollie night, there is no dress code
shiny time is now 煌めいてくよ舞台
Shiny time is now, shining brightly on stage
crazy kureiji dance 心躍るようなジャーニー
Crazy Kureiji dance, a heart-throbbing journey
見つけたんだ とっておきの居場所
I found it, my absolute favorite place
LET'S GO!!
CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!! KUREIJI KUREIJI KUREIJI SUPER!!
MEGA!! HYPER!! SISTER!! CHO KAWAII CHO YABAI!!
OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE OLLIE
hey jollie jollie night let's kureiji party night stay up ya all night long
Hey jollie jollie night, let's Kureiji party night, stay up all night long
jollie jollie jollie yeah
hey jollie jollie night let's kureiji party night stay up ya all night long
Hey jollie jollie night, let's Kureiji party night, stay up all night long
jollie jollie jollie yeah
hey jollie jollie night let's kureiji party night stay up ya all night long
Hey jollie jollie night, let's Kureiji party night, stay up all night long
jollie jollie jollie yeah
hey jollie jollie night let's kureiji party night stay up ya all night long
Hey jollie jollie night, let's Kureiji party night, stay up all night long
jollie jollie jollie yeah
hey jollie jollie night let's kureiji party night stay up ya all night long
Hey jollie jollie night, let's Kureiji party night, stay up all night long
jollie jollie jollie yeah
どうだった？ 3Dどうでしたかー？
How was it? How was the 3D?
選んだJOLLIE JOLLIE、頑張って歌ったJOLLIE JOLLIE、どうだった？みんな楽しんでくれた？
How was "JOLLIE JOLLIE"? Did everyone enjoy it?
ここまで、みんなが来てくれたことが、超奇跡のオリー。
Everyone coming here with me up to this point is a super miracle for Ollie.
一番最初の、そして歌の…最後までみんなが来てくれたことが一番最初。
The very first song... and everyone coming here until the end, my very first...
いや、まぁ、みんな、本当にスタッフのみんな、ありがとうございます！みんな、応援してくれて…！
Well, um, everyone, really, thank you so much to all the staff! And thank you all for your support...!
We actually made it!
And I'm so happy!
Well, I'll be on a bigger stage next time, so until then, see you guys next time!
バイバーイ！またねー！オリー・クレイジー！
Bye-bye! See you next time! Ollie Kureiji!